嗨  大家好
Hey, everyone.
过得还好吧
What's up?
我是Rob Dodson罗布  多德森
It's Rob Dodson.
在今天的Polycasts节目里
In today's episode of Polycasts, I'm
我将向你们展示在使用core-pages元素的应用程序中
going to show you how to dynamically swap around
如何实现动态地切换
all the content in your application using
所有内容  那么开始吧
the core pages element, so check it out.
所有单页应用程序的特点是
The hallmark of any single-page application
当用户浏览不同部分时
is that it doesn't refresh the page
它不会刷新整个页面
as the user is navigating to different sections.
以Polymer网站为例
So using the Polymer site as an example,
你可以看到  当我点击菜单条目时
you can see that, as I'm clicking around the menu items,
页面上的所有内容
all the content on the page is just
都是几乎瞬间改变的
sort of instantaneously changing.
这使得整个应用有非常漂亮和轻快的感觉
It makes the whole app have this really nice, snappy feel to it.
有很多方法可以实现这个效果
Now there's a few ways that you can achieve this effect.
最基本的  也就是我今天要讲的一个
The most basic, and the one that I'll cover today,
包括显示和隐藏在页面上可用的
involves showing and hiding different bits of content that
的不同的内容
are already available on the page,
简单说来就是把一些部分设置为display:block正常显示
basically just telling some to display
而其他的部分设置为display:none不显示
block and others to display none.
还有些其他的办法
There are other strategies which include
包括使用Ajax技术去和你的服务器对话 抓取一些内容
using Ajax to go talk to your server, grab some content,
然后注入到文档中或是输送数据到
and then inject that back into the document or piping data
页面上已经存在的模板中
to templates that you already have that are on the page
然后填充他们
and then sort of inflating them.
好
All right.
我将在未来的课程里讲
I'm going to cover these other two
其他的两个技术  但今天就从一个
techniques in future episodes, but let's start off
简单的例子开始
with a really simple example today
就是让一些部分在显示和不显示间来回切换
just switching some sections on and off.
这里我使用Sublime编辑器 而且已经准备好
So here I am in Sublime, and I've already
建立了一个很简单的工程
gone ahead and set up a really simple project.
在bower.json文件里  我已经包括了core元素
In my bower.json, I've included the core elements
而且把所有内容安装到Bower Components目录里
and installed everything to my Bower Components directory.
那么继续进行  我将做的第一件事情就是
So to get rolling, the first thing I'm going to do
打开elements.html文件且把core-pages元素
is open my elements HTML file and add the core pages
加进去  它就被导入了
elements so it gets imported.
然后  在index.html文件的索引里  我将写出core-pages标签
Then in my index HTML file, I'll write out a core pages tag,
同时把它的selected属性设为0
and I'm going to give it a selected attribute of 0.
我还要进入并且设置些样本
I'm also going to go in and set some kind of boilerplate
内容
content up.
现在  这里的selected属性就很重要了
Now, the selected attribute up here is really important,
而且它工作的方式基本上是这样
and the way it works is it basically
告诉core-pages标签选择哪一个子元素去显示
tells core pages which of its children to display.
这有点类似于数组里的索引
It's kind of like an index on an array.
因此这个子元素将会是子元素0
So this child right here is going to be child 0,
这个子元素会成为子标签1  而这部分会是子元素2
this child is child 1, and this section is going to be child 2.
因为我已经设置selected等于1
Since I've set selected equal to 1,
它将实际上使用了
it's going to actually try to render this portfolio
下面这个portfolio节
section down here.
如果你到Chrome上刷新页面
If you hop on into Chrome and refresh the page,
你应该看到那个portfolio content刚好显示在这里
you should see that portfolio content showing up right there.
但你不局限于使用数字索引
But you're not limited to using a numeric index.
如果你给core-pages元素一个
If you give your core pages element
带值的属性  你可以
a value attribute instead, you can
选择匹配这个值属性的任何子元素
select any child that matches that value attribute.
我要去设定值属性为data-category
I'm going to set value attribute to data category.
这是一个我已经完全做好的属性
This is an attribute that I've just totally made up.
而且我将给每一部分
And I'm going to give each of these sections
一个相应的data-category属性
a matching data category attribute.
现在  如果我设置选择的值为contact  这样就
Now, if I set my selected value to contact, what that does
让core-pages元素使用data-category属性是contact作为匹配值来
is it tells core pages to find the child with a matching data
寻找子元素
category of contact.
看看我们的各个部分  我们可以
Looking through our sections, we can
发现这个刚好匹配
see that this one right down here matches.
因此  当我们跳转到Chrome更新这个页面时
And so, when we hop over to Chrome, refresh the page,
我们会看到我们的Contact部分现在显示出来了
we should see our Contact section is now displaying.
OK  如果你回顾一下上节课
All right, so if you recall in the last episode,
我把所有的元素都放入一个自动绑定的template
I wrapped all of my elements in an auto-binding template
元素里
element.
现在  我们可以做同样的事
Now, we can do the same thing here
来把我们的core页面元素关联到一个菜单
to connect our core pages element to a menu.
让我们看一下
Let's check it out.
好的  我已经加了一些标记到我们的页面中
All right, I've added a little bit more markup to our page,
因此  我们有一个core-drawer-panel元素
so, now we have a core drawer panel.
它包含了我们所有的页面
It's holding all of our pages.
我们也有core-header-panel和core-toolbar元素  一堆在之前课程里
We also have header panels and toolbars, a bunch of elements
讲过的元素
that we've shown in previous episodes.
如果你错过了那些剧集
And if you missed those episodes,
我们下边的显示注释里有相关链接
we've got links to them down in the show notes.
我要做的第一件事就是把所有一切包装
First thing I'm going do is wrap everything
到自动绑定template之内
inside of an auto-binding template,
因此我将使用等于auto-binding的is属性
so I'm going to use that is equals auto-binding attribute,
抓取我们所有的内容粘贴在里边
grab all my content, paste it inside there,
并且也要给我的template元素一个ID属性为app
and also give my template an ID of app,
那样的话之后我可以用Javascript引用它
so that way I can refer to it later using JavaScript.
下一步  我会弹开我的elements.html文件并
Next, I'm going to pop open my elements HTML file and drop
导入一个core-menu.html和一个core-item.html进去
in a core menu and core items imports.
回到我的index.html文件  我将写一个core-menu
And back in my index file, I'll write out a core menu
并用和我们页类别相对应的core-item
and populate it with items that match
来填充它
all of our page categories.
现在是魔法时刻
Now comes the magic moment.
因为core-menu元素和core-pages元素扩展相同的公共父
Because core menu and core pages extend the same common parent
叫做core-selector  这意味着它们
called core selector, it means they
都可以利用到值属性的特性
can both take advantage of value attribute.
我将给这里的每个core-item
I'm going to give each of my core items
一个data-category属性  它们匹配core-page元素的data-category
a data category that matches the core page's data categories,
并且我将设定selected属性值等于一个局部
and I can set my selected value equal to a scope
变量  我正在构造并命名为page
variable, which I'm just going to make up and call page.
接着  我到core-pages部分
Then I can go down to my core pages section
将selected属性赋值为一个局部变量
and give it a scope variable for its selected value,
也叫做page
also called page.
现在  事实上  我已经把这两个元素连接到起来了
And now, in effect, I've linked these two elements,
我的菜单到我的页面
my menu to my pages.
如果我打开Chrome并刷新页面
If I hop open to Chrome and refresh the page,
你将看到我在点击菜单项时
you'll see that as I'm clicking my menu items,
它同时也在更新页面的内容
it's also updating the page content.
为了设置一个默认页面  我要
To set a default page, I'm going to select
在app.js文件里的选择自动绑定template元素
the auto-binding template in my app JS file
并给它的page变量一个初始值
and give it an initial value for its page variable.
我将更进一步并设置page变量等于home
I'll just go ahead and set page equal to home.
现在  当我建立应用程序时
Now when I set up my application,
它会默认显示home网页
it's displaying the home page by default.
好  使用core-pages
All right, now that you can change
在你应用程序中  你可以在不同状态之间改变
between the different states in your application
你可以开始考虑
using core pages, you can start to think
添加像路由这样的额外的东西
about adding additional things like routing.
那也是我们下节课要讲的内容
That's exactly what we're going to cover in the next episode,
所以一定要订阅
so be sure to subscribe.
一定要在下面留下评论
Definitely leave comments down below
让我们知道您的想法
to let us know what you think.
与往常一样  非常感谢您的收看，
As always, thank you so much for watching,
下次再见
and I will see you next time.